neatvideo.com 2019-03-11

# Privacy statement | Neat Video

Cookies are disabled. This site requires cookies turned on to run properly. Please enable cookies and reload this page.

HomePrivacy statement

Effective Date: 21 May 2018

NeatLab has adopted this privacy statement (hereinafter "Privacy Statement") to inform you of its collection and processing of your personal or personally identifiable information through the neatvideo.com website (hereinafter "Website"). NeatLab values your privacy and has adopted this Privacy Statement in an effort to remain transparent with respect to its collection and processing of your personal or personally identifiable information.

NeatLab reserves the right to suspend, replace, modify, amend, or terminate this Privacy Statement at any time and within its sole and absolute discretion. In the event NeatLab replaces, modifies, or amends this Privacy Statement, the Effective Date, located above, will change. Your continued use of the Website after a change in the Effective Date constitutes your manifestation of assent to and agreement to any replacement, modification, or amendment herein.

##  1\. What information may be collected

NeatLab may collect the following personal or personally identifiable information from you or from the payment processors or resellers that handle your orders or otherwise serve you: your full name, organization name (if applicable), e-mail address(es), telephone number, billing and delivery postal addresses, VAT number (if applicable), IP address, browser software, order numbers and payment methods used, receipts issued by the payment processors, dates and times of purchases, names and licenses of the purchased products, use of the Website, messages sent to NeatLab or posted on the Website.

NeatLab may collect this personal or personally identifiable information when you directly contact NeatLab and disclose your identity, order NeatLab's products directly or through resellers, use the Website and your account on the Website, download, register and update the products, request technical support and other assistance from NeatLab.

NeatLab may collect this personal or personally identifiable information through various technical means, including, but not limited to, the following: the Website pages, message forms and bug report forms that may be offered at the Website, forums and blogs that may be hosted at the Website, e-mail messages, session cookies, persistent cookies, web server logs, tracking scripts, third-party e-mail list services including, but not limited to, Mailgun, third-party analytics tools and services, including, but not limited to, Matomo, Google Analytics, etc.

##  2\. How this information is used

NeatLab may use your personal or personally identifiable information to carry out the pre-contractual measures when you want to become a customer of NeatLab and to perform NeatLab's contractual obligations when you are a customer of NeatLab. NeatLab may also use that information in pursuing the legitimate interests of NeatLab such as safety and security of NeatLab, its employees and customers, its products, services and the Website.

NeatLab may use your personal or personally identifiable information for the following specific purposes:

  * To provide you with NeatLab's products and support;
  * To communicate with you about NeatLab's products and services;
  * To transmit information to a third party to aid you in completing a transaction, such as purchasing NeatLab's products and services;
  * To provide you with the Website and its associated services;
  * To advertise and promote NeatLab's products and services;
  * To request information from you in order to improve NeatLab's products or services;
  * To verify that NeatLab's products and services are used in accordance with the terms of the corresponding license agreements;
  * To prevent unauthorized access to and use of your account and products by third parties;
  * To tailor the Website and its content to your preferences;
  * To aid NeatLab in changing the content of the Website or improve the Website usability.

NeatLab keeps your personal or personally identifiable information for as long as you remain a customer of NeatLab and two years after that. After that period, the corresponding information is routinely deleted, provided it is no longer needed for ensuring the legitimate interests of NeatLab and is not required by law.

##  3\. How this information is secured

NeatLab values the security of your personal and personally identifiable information and has implemented industry standard encryption to protect against unauthorized access to or interception of your personal and personally identifiable information. This applies to all information storage resources used by NeatLab and all channels used for transmission of that information between computer systems. Computer systems of NeatLab are protected by the state of the art network firewalls and antivirus software.

You recognize, however, that unencrypted electronic mail is not secure and that you accept all risks associated with contacting NeatLab through unencrypted electronic mail. You are responsible for the security of your electronic communications with NeatLab.

NeatLab may collect and process your personal and personally identifiable information on secure servers located in the United States of America, in the Netherlands, in Australia, and, through your use of the Website, you hereby expressly agree to the processing of your personal and personally identifiable information within the United States of America, the Netherlands, and Australia. You hereby provide your unambiguous consent to the processing of your personal and personally identifiable information.

##  4\. Sharing the information

NeatLab does not sell or rent your personal or personally identifiable information to third parties.

NeatLab may share your personal or personally identifiable information with third party service providers retained by NeatLab, such as payment processors, resellers of NeatLab products and e-mail delivery services to assist you in the process of ordering of NeatLab's products and services, receiving NeatLab's products and services, or to provide you with additional information on the products and services of NeatLab.

NeatLab may, after being authorized by you, share your contact information with NeatLab's industry partners in order to resolve technical problems that involve both products or services provided by those partners and NeatLab's products or services.

NeatLab may, after being authorized by you, publish parts of your feedback or comments about NeatLab's products or services.

NeatLab may also transfer your personal or personally identifiable information to third parties to respond to a duly authorized subpoena or court order, to respond to regulatory requests by government authorities, to protect the safety or security of NeatLab, its employees and customers, its products and the Website, and, where necessary, to protect against fraud, cyberattacks, or any other violation of any law, statute, ordinance, regulation, or treaty whether local, state, provincial, national, or international.

NeatLab may transfer your personal or personally identifiable information to share information with its subsidiaries, affiliates, or distributors or to a third party in a sale of the Website, a sale of NeatLab, or a sale of substantially all of the assets of NeatLab.

##  5\. How you can control your personal data

You can always contact NeatLab if you have any question regarding this Privacy Statement or wish to review, modify or delete your personal data.

Please note that you must always make clear who you are, so that NeatLab could identify the right data and not affect the security of the personal data of any other person. NeatLab may request additional information to verify your identity in such a situation.

##  6\. Notices

All notices to be made to NeatLab pursuant to this Privacy Statement may be made in writing to  e-mail user: info, e-mail domain: neatvideo.com with the subject "Privacy".
